<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Workday to SAP Worker to Employee Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
			
As a Workday admin I want to migrate Workers from Workday to SAP as Employees.

This template leverages the Mule batch module.
The batch job is divided into *Process* and *On Complete* stages.

1. The integration is triggered by an HTTP request. template in batch Input stage queries Workday for active workers created or modified within the configured time frame.
2. In the batch Process stage the matching employee data (if it exists) is fetched from SAP (based on the e-mail) and mapped to the SAP input data structure.
3. Afterwards, each employee data is sent to the destination instance, SAP, where the existing employee is updated or new one is created.
4. Finally, within the *On Complete* stage, the template will provide batch statistics to both the pre-configured e-mail recipient and to the console.

		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
			
			
There are certain pre-requisites that must be considered to run this template. All of them deal with the preparations in both source and destination systems, that must be made for the template to run smoothly. 
**Failing to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**
There are a couple of things you should take into account before running this template:
**Workday email uniqueness**: The email can be repeated for two or more workers (or missing). Therefore Workday workers with duplicate emails will be removed from processing in the Process stage.

## Disclaimer
This Anypoint template uses a few private Maven dependencies from Mulesoft in order to work. If you intend to run this template with Maven support, you need to add three extra dependencies for SAP to the pom.xml.


		</section>
		<section id="sap_dst">

This template uses custom BAPI functions. To create them please use following steps:

1. Create function module `ZHCMFM_NUMBER_GET_NEXT` in transaction `SE37` as per source file `ZHCMFM_NUMBER_GET_NEXT.abap`

Referenced files are in [src/main/resources] directory.

		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">

### Application configuration

+ http.port `9090`
+ page.size `100`
+ migration.startDate `2015-09-18T12:00:00.000Z`


#### Workday Connector configuration
+ wday.username `bob.dylan@orga`
+ wday.tenant `org457`
+ wday.password `DylanPassword123`
+ wday.host `servise425546.workday.com`

### SAP Connector configuration
+ sap.jco.ashost `your.sap.address.com`
+ sap.jco.user `SAP_USER`
+ sap.jco.passwd `SAP_PASS`
+ sap.jco.sysnr `14`
+ sap.jco.client `800`
+ sap.jco.lang `EN`

### SAP HR configuration

+ sap.hire.org.COMP_CODE `3000`
+ sap.hire.org.PERS_AREA `300`
+ sap.hire.org.EMPLOYEE_GROUP `1`
+ sap.hire.org.EMPLOYEE_SUBGROUP `U5`
+ sap.hire.org.PERSONNEL_SUBAREA `0001`
+ sap.hire.org.LEGAL_PERSON `0001`
+ sap.hire.org.PAYROLL_AREA `PR`
+ sap.hire.org.COSTCENTER `4130`
+ sap.hire.org.ORG_UNIT `50000590`
+ sap.hire.org.POSITION `50000046`
+ sap.hire.org.JOB `50052752`
+ sap.hire.personal.PERSIDNO `50052755`
+ sap.hire.hr_infotype.TO_DATE `50052757`
+ sap.hire.default.dob `1980-01-01`

#### SMTP Services configuration
+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `exampleuser@gmail.com`
+ smtp.password `ExamplePassword456`

### Mail details
+ mail.from `batch.migrateworkers.migration%40mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `your.addres@yourcompany.org`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job report`


		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">

There are no special considerations regarding API calls.

		</section>
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		
This file should contain every inbound endpoint of your integration app. It is intended to contain the application API.
In this particular template, this file contains a HTTP connector that listens for HTTP request to specified URL to trigger the batch processing.

		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		
This file holds the functional aspect of the template (points 2. to 4. described in the template overview). Its main component is a Batch job, and it includes *steps* for executing the broadcast operation from Workday to SAP.

	</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>