<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Workday to SAP Worker to Employee Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
			<![CDATA[
As a Workday admin I want to migrate Workers from Workday to SAP as Employees.

This Anypoint Template leverages the [Batch Module](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing).
The batch job is divided into *Input*, *Process* and *On Complete* stages.

1. The integration is triggered by an HTTP request. Anypoint Template in batch Input stage will query Workday for active workers created or modified within the configured time frame.
2. In the batch Process stage the matching employee data (if it exists) is fetched from SAP (based on the e-mail) and mapped to the SAP input data structure.
3. Afterwards, each employee data is sent to the destination instance, SAP, where the existing employee is updated or new one is created.
4. Finally, within the *On Complete* stage, the Anypoint Template will provide batch statistics to both the pre-configured e-mail recipient and to the console.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
			<![CDATA[
			
There are certain pre-requisites that must be considered to run this Anypoint Template. All of them deal with the preparations in both source and destination systems, that must be made in order for all to run smoothly. **Failling to do so could lead to unexpected behavior of the template.**
There are a couple of things you should take into account before running this Anypoint Template:
**Workday email uniqueness**: The email can be repeated for two or more workers (or missing). Therefore Workday workers with duplicate emails will be removed from processing in the Input stage.

## Disclaimer

This Anypoint template uses a few private Maven dependencies in order to work. If you intend to run this template with Maven support, please continue reading.

You will find that there are three dependencies in the pom.xml file that begin with the following group id: 
	**com.sap.conn.jco** 
These dependencies are private for Mulesoft and therefore your application will not build from a Maven command line. You need to replace them with "provided" scope and copy the libraries into the build path.

]]>
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
<![CDATA[
### Common configuration

+ http.port `9090`
+ migration.startDate `2015-09-18T12:00:00.000Z`

#### Workday Connector configuration
+ wday.user `admin@workday`
+ wday.password `secret`
+ wday.endpoint `https://impl-cc.workday.com/ccx/service/workday/Human_Resources/v21.1`

### SAP Connector configuration

+ sap.jco.ashost `your.sap.address.com`
+ sap.jco.user `SAP_USER`
+ sap.jco.passwd `SAP_PASS`
+ sap.jco.sysnr `14`
+ sap.jco.client `800`
+ sap.jco.lang `EN`

### SAP HR configuration

+ sap.hire.org.COMP_CODE `3000`
+ sap.hire.org.PERS_AREA `300`
+ sap.hire.org.EMPLOYEE_GROUP `1`
+ sap.hire.org.EMPLOYEE_SUBGROUP `U5`
+ sap.hire.org.PERSONNEL_SUBAREA `0001`
+ sap.hire.org.LEGAL_PERSON `0001`
+ sap.hire.org.PAYROLL_AREA `PR`
+ sap.hire.org.COSTCENTER `4130`
+ sap.hire.org.ORG_UNIT `50000590`
+ sap.hire.org.POSITION `50000046`
+ sap.hire.org.JOB `50052752`
+ sap.hire.default.dob `1980-01-01`

### SMTP Services configuration
+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `your_username`
+ smtp.password `your_password`

### Mail details
+ mail.from `batch.migrateworkers.migration%40mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `your.addres@yourcompany.org`
+ mail.subject `Batch Job report`

]]>
		</section>
		<section id="api_calls">
<![CDATA[
There are no special considerations regarding API calls.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This file should contain every inbound endpoint of your integration app. It is intended to contain the application API.
In this particular template, this file contains a HTTP connector that listens for HTTP request to specified URL to trigger the batch processing.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This file holds the functional aspect of the template (points 2. to 3. described in the template overview). Its main component is a Batch job, and it includes *steps* for executing the broadcast operation from Workday to SAP.
]]>
	</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>